[
  {
    "question": "首字母填词并回答问题",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Human and pets b() have feelings.",
    "answers": ["both"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We laugh a() smile to show that we are happy. ",
    "answers": ["and"]
  },
  {
    "question": "But dogs wag tails to tell us they f() happy. ",
    "answers": ["feel"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you see cats attack or bite, that shows they are v() angry.",
    "answers": ["very"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your pets and you can be friends if you l() and understand e() other.",
    "answers": ["love each"]
  },
  {
    "question": "1.Do human and pets have feeling?",
    "answers": ["Yes, they do."]
  },
  {
    "question": "2.What do dogs do when they are happy?",
    "answers": ["Wag tails", "Wag tails."]
  },
  {
    "question": "3.Why are pets friendly to us? Because ()",
    "answers": ["we love and understand each other"]
  },
  {
    "question": "4.How can we know the cats are angry?",
    "answers": ["Attack or bite."]
  },
  {
    "question": "圈出错误处，把正确答案写在横线上",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "How much milk are there in the bottle?",
    "answers": ["is"]
  },
  {
    "question": "He usually go to the bookstore with his mother.",
    "answers": ["goes"]
  }
]
